Finding Aid for the Collection of Reprints and Facsimile Reproductions of Various American Newspapers LSC.0090
UCLA Library Special Collections
Reprints and Facsimile Reproductions of Various American Newspapers collection
1728-1968
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.0090
1 unknown (1 oversize box, 19 folders)
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942328653606533
Scope and Content
Collection consists of reprints and facsimile reproductions of issues of various American newspapers and historical headlines from the Los Angeles times of twentieth century Presidential elections (1900-1968). Also includes Ulster County Gazette (1800), The Daily Citizen (1863), The New York Herald (1865), The Creede Chronicle (1892), The Solid Muldoon (1879), Rocky Mountain Herald (1860), The Fresno Morning Republican (1920), The Los Angeles Daily Times (1881), The Los Angeles Times (1906), The Illustrated San Diego Herald (1853), The Los Angeles Star (1851), The Weekly Observer (1888), Californian (1846), Daily Dispatch (1861), Daily National Intelligencer (1861), The Maryland Journal (1773), The New England Weekly Journal (1728), and The Worcester Gazette (1790).
Newspapers.; Online resources.
- Ulster County Gazette, January 4, 1800. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  Kingston, Ulster County. vol.2 no.88 (3 examples).
- The Vicksburg Daily Citizen [the Wallpaper Edition of], July 2, 1863. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Vicksburg, Mississippi (5 examples).
- The New York Herald, April 15 and 16, 1865. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  New York, New York. April 15 (6 examples) -photocopies of examples 2 and 4-6. April 16 (1 example).
  USE PHOTOCOPIES ONLY.
- The Creede Chronicle, March 22, 1892. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Creede, Colorado. vol.1 no.1.
- The Solid Muldoon, September 5, 1879. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Ouray, California. vol.1 no.1.
- Rocky Mountain Herald, May 5, 1860. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Denver, Colorado. vol.1 no.1.
- The Fresno Morning Republican, January 11, 1920. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Fresno, California. vol.57 no.11 (Front page only).
- The Los Angeles Daily Times, December 4, 1881. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Los Angeles, California. vol.1 no.1.
- The Los Angeles Times, April 21, 1906. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Los Angeles, California (Front page only).
- The Illustrated San Diego Herald, October 1, 1853. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  San Diego, California. vol.3 no.34.
- The Los Angeles Star, May 17, 1851. (Box 1, Folder 11)
- The Weekly Observer, October 20, 1888. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Los Angeles, California. vol.1 no.1. Negatives included. 2 copies of different sizes.
- Historical Headlines: Famous Front Pages of the Los Angeles Times, 1900-1968. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Los Angeles, California. 4th edition. Presidential Elections of the Twentieth Century.
- Californian, August 15, 1846. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Monterey, California. vol.1 no.1.
- Daily Dispatch, April 13, 1861. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Richmond, Virginia. vol.19 no.86.
- Daily National Intelligencer, April 13, 1861. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Washington, D.C. vol.49 no.15,187.
- The Maryland Journal, August 20, 1773. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Baltimore, Maryland. (pp. 2-3 only).
- The New England Weekly Journal, April 8, 1728. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Boston, Massachusetts. no.55.
- Massachusetts SPD: or, the Worcester Gazette, August 5, 1790. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Worcester, Massachusetts. vol.19 no.905.